What took her family years to build, a stranger stole in an instant.
Trust is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by David Schwimmer.
A suburban family is torn apart when fourteen-year-old
Annie meets her first boyfriend online.
After months of communicating via online chat and phone, Annie
discovers her friend is not who he originally claimed to be.
Shocked into disbelief, her parents are shattered by their daughter's actions and struggle to
support her as she comes to terms with what has happened to her once innocent life.
William "Will" Cameron, played by Clive Owen.
Lynn Cameron, played by Catherine Keener.
Annie Cameron, played by Liana Liberato.
FBI Agent Doug Tate, played by Jason Clarke.
Gail Friedman, played by Viola Davis.
Mr. Weston, played by Chris Henry Coffey.
Trust (stylized as trust_) is a 2010 American drama thriller film directed by David Schwimmer and
written by Andy Bellin and Robert Festinger based on an uncredited story by Schwimmer.
Starring Clive Owen, Catherine Keener, Jason Clarke, Liana Liberato, and Viola Davis, the film follows a fourteen-year-old
girl who becomes a victim of sexual abuse after meeting a man posing as a teenage boy on an online chat room.
Trust premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 10, 2010, and was
given a limited theatrical release in the United States on April 1, 2011.
The film received positive reviews, with Liberato's
performance earning critical praise.
Liberato won the Silver Hugo Award for Best Actress at the Chicago International Film Festival, and
Schwimmer was nominated for the Grand Special Prize at the Deauville American Film Festival.
The film explores themes of pedophilia, high
school, child abuse, rape, sexual abuse.
The tone is emotional and intense.